

Personal

Name Batuhan Tibet Ayaydın

Address Körfez Mah. Hünriyet Blv. No:25 55100 Samsun/Atakum

Phone number +905533016155

Email tibet.ayaydin@gmail.com

Date of birth 10-10-1999

Place of birth Samsun

Gender Male

Marital status Single

Driving licence B, A, AM

Website blibet github io

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/tibetayay

Batuhan Tibet Ayaydın

I am a Unity Game Developer with 2 years of experience. I can create hyper-casual and basic games for you. I can develop games with simple mechanics, addictive gameplay, and appealing visuals. Whether you need a quick and engaging mobile game or a straightforward desktop game,

Work experience

Game Developer Aug 2021 - Feb 2022
Lebleby Games, Samsun/Atakum

Feb 2022 - Feb 2023

Head of Development Leleby Games, Samsun/Atakum

Education and Qualifications

Bilgisayar Mühendisliği Diploması Sep 2018 - Jun 2023 Ondokuz Mayıs Üniversitesi, Samsun

Languages

English
Turkish

Skills

Unity
Adobe Photoshop
FL Studio
C#
HTML/CSS
Blender
Java

Interests

Gaming Watching Movies and Series Basketball